Hi, welcome to this course.
Before you start, let me explain you a few things.
See, the first point is how to follow this course.
See if you have taken this course for academic purposes.
If you have Java programming as your subject, then I suggest you follow the codes right from the beginning
and follow the lectures in the same order.
Don't skip anything.
Whatever the section that comes under your syllabus, you can cover them if any section is not in the
syllabus.
You can skip it the next.
If you already know Java and you are preparing for campus interviews and already you know the things,
then you can skip the topics.
But whichever topic you're selecting, please make sure that you are listening to all the lectures in
that section.
If you directly jump on a particular video, then you may not understand everything from it because
the topics are related in a particular section.
So please start the section from the beginning, although I don't directly jump on a particular topic
inside a section.
And if you are from industry and if you want to brush up any particular topic, then you can go ahead.
You might be having working experience.
Also, you can watch any lecture.
Then the next thing is about ressource.
Fee for the coding lectures where I am showing you the program.
So after watching that lecture, you try to write on the program by yourself.
And if you face any difficulty, then you can go to resources, you can download the resource.
That same program is available in the form of a resource.
You can click on the link and download it.
So just beside that lecture on the return site, you'll find a list of lectures, right?
So under the same lecture, the one you are watching, you will find a link called Resource.
Click on it and the program will be downloaded on your machine.
Make sure that the popup blocker is disappeared and still, if you face any difficulty, you are unable
to remove the error, then you can contact me in question answer section just below every lecture down
here.
On the right hand side, just below the belly button, you'll find Kushan answers.
So question answers.
You can ask a question.
And if the question is related to the code, then I suggest you copy paste the code there so that I
can easily check your program and help you with the errors.
So that's all go ahead and try to watch it without skipping any lectures.